Hello.
Next, I want to display the amount of life that my character has on our HUD.
So if we go over to the Widget Blueprint folder and go over to the images folder, then attached in
this course lecture file.
I'm going to make sure to include these two images.
Just drag both of them in.
You will see why we drag in the apple again in a second.
Then if we select both of the images, right click and go explore actions and apply paper to detect
the settings.
Then if we head over to the player hard and on the palette, look for a horizontal box.
And just drag this into this vegetable box.
Then look for an image and just track this into the horizontal box.
Then look for a piece of text and drag this into the same horizontal box.
Put the image, select the head image that we just imported.
Then in the x, just adjust it size until it looks a bit normal.
Then select the text.
And just check this is variable and call it lives.
Then if we go over to the graph.
After we tell the game to set our apples and Macs apples text, we want to drag in our life's text and
drag up here and look for set text and set this one, set, text, text.
We will then drag in our SE player VP reference and get them out of life so that they have and then
connect this into here and this into here.
So now if I go compile and play when I die, it should update my life to two.
Okay, so it didn't update my lives.
If I go back to my BP, we'll investigate What's wrong?
Okay, because I'm saying my life's after we show our HUD.
The game is not accurately showing the amount of lifestyle I have, so I'm actually just going to move
these nodes before we show our heart.
So if I just press out, it'll break the link here and here, and I'm just going to copy these notes.
And I'm going to move them to.
I set my health and then I set my lives, and then I'll just connect these nodes.
So now if I go compile and play.
And I die.
When I die, I should update my life's.
A guy died and then an update to my life's.
Next, if we go back to our layout and to the designer and just delete.
Actually, no.
So for this Apple image, the reason it looks kind of weird is if I just click the search one.
And go over to this apple.
It's because this apple, it has loads of invisible area that's taking up.
That's why I got to import a new apple image.
And if we just in the palette look for an image and just drag this into the first horizontal box and
just select these arrows and move the image to the start.
Put this image.
Select it and then select the new apple that I made us import and just increase.
It sets in the X until it looks normal.
And then we can delete this vertical box.
And one more thing.
If I just let this horizontal box and go to padding and on the bottom, if I put a value of like 20,
then there's going to be a bit of a gap between this box and this box and never go compile and play.
Visually, I think that just looks a bit better.